We'll be starting with this image of a car on a green screen background.
刚开始 我们先看看绿色屏幕背景上的这幅汽车图像
We'll first have to identify this green region,
首先 我们必须识别绿色区域
then later you'll replace it with a background image.
然后 你可以将其替换为背景图像
We're in a python notebook,
我们打开了一个 Python 笔记本
and my first step is to import the libraries I need,
第一步是导入我们需要的库
and we will use these throughout this lesson.
我们整堂课都会使用这些
For plotting and reading im images,
要绘制并读入图像
I'll import matplotlib.pyplot im image.
我会导入 matplotlib.pyplot 和 matplotlib.image
For operating on an image,
要在图像上操作
I'll use numpy and the computer vision library open cv which is named "cv2".
我会使用 numpy 和计算机视觉库 opencv 名称为 cv2
Next, you can see I've read in the image of the car using "mpimg.imread."
接下来 你可以看到 我已经使用 mpimg.imread 读入了汽车图像
This image is in the same directory as this notebook in a folder named "images."
这幅图和笔记本在同一个文件夹下 文件夹叫 images
Once it's read in, I'll actually want to print out some information about the image.
读入之后 我想打印一些图像的信息
This information will be helpful later when you want to add
后面 你想向绿色部分添加不同背景时
a different background to the green section.
该信息会比较有用
So, I'll print in shape which will tell us the dimensions of the image,
我这里打印了 shape 它会告诉我们图像大小
and also I'll display the image.
这里是显示图像
And we see the expected output.
我们看到了预期的输出
The image is an array of values and its shape contains
图像是由值组成的一个阵列 它的形状包括
three values that represent the dimensions of the image array.
三个值 单表了图像阵列的大小
First, it's height; 450 pixels,
首先 高度 450 像素
then it's width; 660 pixels.
汽车 宽度 660 像素
And finally, how many color components it has?
最后 它有多少颜色分量？
In this case, three.
在本例中 有 3 个
One for red, green and blue values.
红色、绿色和蓝色值各一个。
Okay, now that we have our green screen image,
OK 我们现在得到了绿色屏幕图像
let's jump into green screen masking.
我们开始绿色屏幕遮罩
And masking just means blocking out a certain area of an image.
遮罩的意思是 屏蔽图像中的部分区域
To create a mask,
要创建一个遮罩
I'll create a color threshold.
我首先创建一个颜色阈值
I'll define lower and upper bounds for the color I want to isolate, green.
定义我要隔离的颜色 绿色 的颜色上限和下限
So I'll define a lower threshold that contains the lowest values of red,
这里定义一个下限 包括仍被视作绿色屏幕背景的一部分的
green and blue that are still considered part of the green screen background.
红色、绿色和蓝色的最低值
This will be an array of three values in the order;
这是按顺序的三个值的阵列
red, green and blue value.
红色、绿色和蓝色值
For red and blue,
对红色和蓝色
I'll set these is as zero.
我会把这些设为 0
Meaning, it's okay to have no red or blue when identifying this green screen area.
意思是 识别这个绿色屏幕区域时 可以没有红色或蓝色
But the lowest value for green should still be quite high.
但绿色的最低值仍然要很高
Not all the way up to 255,
用不着高到 255
but let's say 200.
我们这里选 200
Then I'll define the upper threshold.
然后 我定义上限
I'll define it to allow a little more red and blue. Say, 50 each.
定义时 我会允许多一点红色和蓝色 比如 每个都设为 50
And I'll set the highest value for green to be 255.
我把绿色的最高值设为 255
Now any color within this range between the low and high thresholds,
现在 上限和下限的区间内的任何颜色
will be an intense green color.
都是明亮的绿色
I am doing some estimation though,
但我现在只是在估算
so if I find that this range isn't finding the green screen area that I want,
因此 如果我发现这个范围找不到我想要的绿色屏幕
I'll come back and change these values.
我会回到这里 更改这些值
Next, I'll use these color thresholds to create an image mask.
接下来 我会使用这些颜色阈值创建一个图像遮罩
Masks are a very common way to isolate
遮罩是很常用的方式 可以隔离
a selected area of interest and do something with that area.
感兴趣的选择区域 并对其进行一些操作
We can create a mask over the green area using open CVs "inRange" function.
我们使用 opencv 的 inRange 函数在绿色区域上创建一个遮罩
This function takes any in image and our lower and upper color thresholds.
这个函数代入一个图像和我们的颜色下限和上限